trumaker.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Trumaker

Trumaker collects customer information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience. We know you care about how your information is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust. The information we collect is only used to communicate with customers about our products, services and promotions.

By accessing, browsing or otherwise using this Website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy.

##### INFORMATION COLLECTED

Two types of information are collected from visitors of our website: personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information. If you purchase our products or services, we will need certain personally identifiable information including contact information (name, email address and shipping address) and financial information (credit card number and expiration date) for order forms and billing purposes, as well as to contact you if any problems occur.

Our website may incorporate "pixel tags", "cookies" or similar tracking technologies that allow us to track the actions of visitors of our website. Pixel tags and cookies are used to collect non- personally identifiable information.

We may aggregate your information with similar data collected from other visitors to improve our website and the products, services, applications, content and features provided. We do not use non-personally identifiable information in any way to create and maintain a personal profile of you, nor collect personally identifiable information.

##### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

Now normally, personally identifiable information collected through use of our website is not shared with unaffiliated third parties. However, we must provide a certain extent of information to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees for them to complete necessary services.

We also reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information collected to any third party if we believe that we are required to: comply with the law, comply with legal processes or governmental requests, prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of our website or our network and/or protect the rights, property, safety and security of Trumaker and its employees, our website visitors, and/or the public.

##### CHANGING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

If you contact us by email through our website, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence in order to respond to you, as well as to send you marketing materials of our products and services. Your information will not be shared with outside parties.

If you would like to change your personally identifiable information or would like it to be removed from our database, feel free to email us at [support@trumaker.com](mailto:support@trumaker.com). For your convenience, you can hit the "unsubscribe" link in our emails if you no longer wish to receive materials from us.

##### SECURITY

Trumaker employs top physical, electronic, and administrative safety measures that meet or exceed current federal standards to protect you. While we are very concerned with safeguarding your information-unfortunately, no security system or method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, so we cannot guarantee the security of our servers. Take your own precautions as well to further protect yourself during such transactions.

##### MODIFICATION OF POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy to better serve our customers, so check in occasionally to review any changes made. You can track updates by referring to the "Effective as of" date at the top of this page.

##### DISCLOSURE IN BUSINESS TRANSFERS

As with any other business, there is a possibility that we may merge with or be acquired by another company; if this happens, the successor company may acquire the data we've collected from our customers. Regardless, Personally Identifiable Information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

##### PRIVACY POLICIES OF THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on Trumaker's site. Other websites that may be accessible through this website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices, so be sure to review the website's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

Trumaker takes your privacy seriously. We are committed to bringing our customers the very best products and service, and that includes a safe and secure shopping experience for the complete package-your trust matters to us. Questions, comments or suggestions? Shoot us an email at [support@trumaker.com](mailto:support@trumaker.com)

Thanks for dropping by.
